Textbox11	Textbox3	Textbox2	Textbox9	Textbox12	Textbox8																			
RCV Detailed Report	General Election	State of Alaska	8-Nov-22																					
																								
Textbox24	Textbox21	Textbox53	state	timeStamp																				
House District 11	Unofficial results	Number of positions to elect is 1.	All Positions Filled	11/23/2022 16:17																				
																								
Textbox36	Textbox41	winnersByThreshold	usesDistricts	previousRoundsEvaluation	eliminationType	fixedPrecisionDecimals	performEliminationTransferInLastRound	skipOvervotedRankings	votesToInThresholdCalculation	useFirstRoundSuspension	skipRankingsRule													
IRV	TRUE	FALSE	TRUE	None	Single	0	TRUE	FALSE	Continuing ballots per round	FALSE	Exhausted on Two or More Ranks Skipped													
																								
Textbox35	Textbox86	choiceName2	votes	Textbox17	points	continuingVotes	points1	choiceName3	votes1	points2	nonTransferableVotes	nonTransferablePoints	surplus	Textbox14	choiceName4	Textbox2	Textbox21	Textbox44	Textbox47	sourceChoiceName	choiceName	ballotsTransferred3	transferFraction3	votes5
State of Alaska	Round 1	"Featherly, Walter T."	"3,480"	45.42%	0	"7,661"	0				519	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 1	"Bieling, Ross P."	"1,183"	15.44%	0	"7,661"	0				519	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 1	"Coulombe, Julie"	"2,998"	39.13%	0	"7,661"	0				519	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 1	Blanks	516	6.74%	0	"7,661"	0				519	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 1	Exhausted	0	0.00%	0	"7,661"	0				519	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 1	Overvotes	3	0.04%	0	"7,661"	0				519	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 1	Remainder Points	0	0.00%	0	"7,661"	0				519	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 1					"7,661"	0	"Featherly, Walter T."	"3,480"	0	519	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 1					"7,661"	0	"Bieling, Ross P."	"1,183"	0	519	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 1					"7,661"	0	"Coulombe, Julie"	"2,998"	0	519	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 1					"7,661"	0	Blanks	516	0	519	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 1					"7,661"	0	Exhausted	0	0	519	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 1					"7,661"	0	Overvotes	3	0	519	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 1					"7,661"	0	Remainder Points	0	0	519	0	0											
State of Alaska														A tie occurred during 										
State of Alaska														A tie occurred during 										
State of Alaska														A tie occurred during 										
State of Alaska														A tie occurred during 										
State of Alaska														A tie occurred during 										
State of Alaska														A tie occurred during 										
State of Alaska														A tie occurred during 										
State of Alaska															"Featherly, Walter T."									
State of Alaska															"Bieling, Ross P."									
State of Alaska															"Coulombe, Julie"									
State of Alaska															Blanks									
State of Alaska															Exhausted									
State of Alaska															Overvotes									
State of Alaska															Remainder Points									
State of Alaska																"The tie is broken by selecting Featherly, Walter T.."								
State of Alaska																"The tie is broken by selecting Bieling, Ross P.."								
State of Alaska																"The tie is broken by selecting Coulombe, Julie."								
State of Alaska																The tie is broken by selecting Blanks.								
State of Alaska																The tie is broken by selecting Exhausted.								
State of Alaska																The tie is broken by selecting Overvotes.								
State of Alaska																The tie is broken by selecting Remainder Points.								
State of Alaska																	"Featherly, Walter T. is  because "							
State of Alaska																	"Bieling, Ross P. is eliminated because the candidate had the least amount of votes."							
State of Alaska																	"Coulombe, Julie is  because "							
State of Alaska																	Blanks is  because 							
State of Alaska																	Exhausted is  because 							
State of Alaska																	Overvotes is  because 							
State of Alaska																	Remainder Points is  because 							
State of Alaska																		 transfer for candidate .	 ballots have been transferred in the following manner:		Blanks			
State of Alaska																		 transfer for candidate .	 ballots have been transferred in the following manner:		Overvotes			
State of Alaska																		 transfer for candidate .	 ballots have been transferred in the following manner:		Remainder Points			
State of Alaska																		"Elimination transfer for candidate Bieling, Ross P.."	1183 ballots have been transferred in the following manner:	"Bieling, Ross P."	"Featherly, Walter T."	81	1	81
State of Alaska																		"Elimination transfer for candidate Bieling, Ross P.."	1183 ballots have been transferred in the following manner:	"Bieling, Ross P."	"Bieling, Ross P."	1183	1	"-1,183"
State of Alaska																		"Elimination transfer for candidate Bieling, Ross P.."	1183 ballots have been transferred in the following manner:	"Bieling, Ross P."	"Coulombe, Julie"	673	1	673
State of Alaska																		"Elimination transfer for candidate Bieling, Ross P.."	1183 ballots have been transferred in the following manner:	"Bieling, Ross P."	Exhausted	429	1	429
State of Alaska	Round 2	"Featherly, Walter T."	"3,561"	49.24%	0	"7,232"	0				948	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 2	"Bieling, Ross P."	0	0.00%	0	"7,232"	0				948	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 2	"Coulombe, Julie"	"3,671"	50.76%	0	"7,232"	0				948	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 2	Blanks	516	7.13%	0	"7,232"	0				948	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 2	Exhausted	429	5.93%	0	"7,232"	0				948	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 2	Overvotes	3	0.04%	0	"7,232"	0				948	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 2	Remainder Points	0	0.00%	0	"7,232"	0				948	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 2					"7,232"	0	"Featherly, Walter T."	"3,561"	0	948	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 2					"7,232"	0	"Bieling, Ross P."	0	0	948	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 2					"7,232"	0	"Coulombe, Julie"	"3,671"	0	948	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 2					"7,232"	0	Blanks	516	0	948	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 2					"7,232"	0	Exhausted	429	0	948	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 2					"7,232"	0	Overvotes	3	0	948	0	0											
State of Alaska	Round 2					"7,232"	0	Remainder Points	0	0	948	0	0											
State of Alaska														A tie occurred during 										
State of Alaska														A tie occurred during 										
State of Alaska														A tie occurred during 										
State of Alaska														A tie occurred during 										
State of Alaska														A tie occurred during 										
State of Alaska														A tie occurred during 										
State of Alaska														A tie occurred during 										
State of Alaska															"Featherly, Walter T."									
State of Alaska															"Bieling, Ross P."									
State of Alaska															"Coulombe, Julie"									
State of Alaska															Blanks									
State of Alaska															Exhausted									
State of Alaska															Overvotes									
State of Alaska															Remainder Points									
State of Alaska																"The tie is broken by selecting Featherly, Walter T.."								
State of Alaska																"The tie is broken by selecting Bieling, Ross P.."								
State of Alaska																"The tie is broken by selecting Coulombe, Julie."								
State of Alaska																The tie is broken by selecting Blanks.								
State of Alaska																The tie is broken by selecting Exhausted.								
State of Alaska																The tie is broken by selecting Overvotes.								
State of Alaska																The tie is broken by selecting Remainder Points.								
State of Alaska																	"Featherly, Walter T. is eliminated because the candidate was not elected in the last round."							
State of Alaska																	"Bieling, Ross P. is  because "							
State of Alaska																	"Coulombe, Julie is elected because all other candidates have been eliminated."							
State of Alaska																	Blanks is  because 							
State of Alaska																	Exhausted is  because 							
State of Alaska																	Overvotes is  because 							
State of Alaska																	Remainder Points is  because 							
State of Alaska																		 transfer for candidate .	 ballots have been transferred in the following manner:		"Featherly, Walter T."			
State of Alaska																		 transfer for candidate .	 ballots have been transferred in the following manner:		"Bieling, Ross P."			
State of Alaska																		 transfer for candidate .	 ballots have been transferred in the following manner:		"Coulombe, Julie"			
State of Alaska																		 transfer for candidate .	 ballots have been transferred in the following manner:		Blanks			
State of Alaska																		 transfer for candidate .	 ballots have been transferred in the following manner:		Exhausted			
State of Alaska																		 transfer for candidate .	 ballots have been transferred in the following manner:		Overvotes			
State of Alaska																		 transfer for candidate .	 ballots have been transferred in the following manner:		Remainder Points			
